injobshub.com 2014-12-19

# Privacy Policy | InJobsHub

We at www.injobshub.com are serious about maintaining privacy of our visitors. Any personal information provided by you including Name, Website, Email etc. will never be provided to anyone outside www.injobshub.com. We collect your E-mail address if you want to subscribe to E-mail Updates. Proper information on unsubscribing is also provided in E-mails sent by us.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.injobshub.com makes use of log files. The information in the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

A “cookie” is a small text file which is placed in your computer to allow us to recognize you the next time you visit our site. www.injobshub.com does not use cookies to collect information. However, we work with online advertising companies that may use these cookies. These third party content providers do not access any of your personal information provided to us (Including Name, E-mail Address, Phone Number). www.injobshub.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.injobshub.com.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.injobshub.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.injobshub.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for detailed information on their Privacy practices and for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.injobshub.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change the privacy policy terms in future which will be available in this page. For any further questions, you may reach us at info.injobshub@gmail.com .
